Guide to the Timothy Dwight College, Yale University, Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Timothy Dwight College, Yale University, photographs
1934-1938
RU 602
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
3.25
The materials consist of photographs documenting the construction of Timothy Dwight College at Yale. Included are interior and exterior views and photographs of the master's house.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 46-B (YRG 46-B), Records and materials documenting individual Yale buildings, facilities, and grounds.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged in four series: I. Construction Progress Photographs, 1934-1935. II. General Views, 1934-1938. III. Oversize. IV. Slides and transparencies.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of photographs documenting the construction of Timothy Dwight College at Yale. Included are interior and exterior views and photographs of the master's house.
College buildings -- Design and construction; Slides (photographs); Photographs; Timothy Dwight College (Yale University); Yale University -- Pictorial works; Yale University -- Buildings; Yale University -- Student housing
- Construction Progress Photographs, 1934-1935; Series I
  - 1934 Aug: excavation (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1934 Sept-Oct (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1934 Nov-Dec (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1935 Jan-Feb (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1935 Mar-Apr (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1935 May-June (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1935 July-Aug (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1935 Sept (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1935 Sept: exterior views (Box 1, Folder 9)
- General views, 1934-1938; Series II
  - Construction views (general), undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Exterior, from street, Circa 1935-1936 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Clock tower, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Courtyard, 1937, n.d (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Master's House, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "Town Hall", undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Interior, dining hall, 1935-1938 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Architect's drawing, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Oversize, Series III
  - Town Hall (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Slides and transparencies, Series IV
  - Slides (Box 4)
  - Transparencies of Courtyard (Box 5)